destinylfg.com 2018-08-19

# Privacy Policy - For The Win

## Last Updated: November 7, 2016

This Privacy Policy is provided to better inform those who are concerned with how their personally identifiable information (PII) is being used online. PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify a single person. Please read our Privacy Policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle PII in connection with your use of our website, user forum, or mobile app (“Site”).

## **What PII do we collect from the people who visit our Site?**

We collect PII from you in a variety of ways when you use the Site or interact with us online, including when you:

  * register on the Site, in which case we receive the information you provide (such as your name, e-mail address, player profile information such as what games and when you typically play and for how long, and any usernames you may provide for Facebook or Twitter) as well as verification information associated with your current registration for video gaming website or network such as the PlayStation Network or Xbox Live;
  * register for our newsletter, in which case we receive your name and e-mail address;
  * respond to a survey or marketing communication, in which case we receive your contact information and any responses to our survey;
  * post on the Site’s user forum, in which case we receive the contents of your posting (and you should note that all posted content and your username will be viewable by third parties);
  * navigate the Site or interact with one of our social media pages, in which case we receive activity-related information as described below (in addition, please see the following sections below: “Social media,” “Do we use cookies?”, and “Online tracking / Do-Not-Track signals”); and
  * transaction information, such as your payment card data and billing address, if you enter into any payment transactions with us.

When you visit the Site, we automatically log PII and non-PII information concerning your activity on the Site. This may include your IP address or device identifier, your browser type, and the types of information you search for and view on the Site. If you arrived at our Site by clicking on an advertisement or promotion on another website, we may also take note of the web page you visited before you came to our Site.

## **How do we use PII?**

We use your PII to provide services and offerings to you, and so that we can provide you with information we think might be of interest. For example, we use your PII to:

  * personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content offerings in which you are most interested;
  * improve the Site in order to better serve you;
  * better respond to your requests;
  * allow you to engage or communicate with others through the Site;
  * administer contests, promotions, surveys or other Site features that we may make available from time to time; and
  * send periodic e-mails regarding the Site or other products and services we believe may be of interest to you.

Note that PII will also be shared with other Site users for the purpose(s) for which it was provided. For example, your user name and player profile information may be shared with other users to match you for gaming and communication purposes).

## **Gaming networks**

We may ask that you follow a verification procedure to verify that you are a current registered user of a video gaming website or network such as the PlayStation Network or Xbox Live. If we actually receive any of the information you provide in connection with any such procedure, we will not use it for any purpose other than verification.

## **Social media**

The collection and use of information on social media websites and applications is governed by the privacy policies of those social media websites and applications. Please remember that any information posted on social media is or may become public.

We may receive information from social media sites, platforms, or applications when you connect to the Site through a social media website, or when you interact with us using social media tools. For example, if you login to the Site using Facebook, we may receive your Facebook id, profile picture, email, first name & last name. If you login to the Site using Twitter we may also receive your Twitter id, profile picture, email, first name & last name. Also, when you “like,” “subscribe to,” or send a “tweet” to us through a social media channel, we may receive your username, handle, or other available information from the social media website or application.

Note that we also may obtain limited social media profile and activity data to the extent available from third parties, and we may combine that information with other information we have about you, for marketing purposes and to tailor the features of our Site.

All information received from social media websites and applications (or from third parties concerning social media activity) is treated and used in the same manner and for the same purposes as described in this Policy with respect to similar information we obtain through the Site.

## **How do we protect PII?**

We have in place reasonable, commercially standard technological and operational security measures to protect PII from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. By way of example, PII is maintained by us within secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have access rights to such systems and are required to keep the information confidential. While we may implement measures to improve the security of online communication, you should remember that no form of electronic communication is 100% secure. Care should be taken whenever you send or receive information online or via e-mail, and heightened care is warranted whenever you are using a public network or unsecured wi-fi connection.

## **Do we use “cookies”?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a website places on your computer’s hard drive through your web browser that enables the Site’s systems and certain third parties (discussed below) to recognize your browser and capture and remember Site usage information. Cookies are used for several purposes.

Some cookies, referred to as “necessary cookies,” are essential for you to move around within the Site and for the operation and security of the Site. Other cookies help us understand your preferences based on previous or current Site activity, which enables the Site to provide you with quality services. We also use cookies (sometimes referred to as “performance cookies”) to help us compile aggregate and analytics data about Site usage, traffic, performance, and interactions so that we can offer better Site experiences and tools in the future. Performance cookies may also be used to gather information for marketing purposes, and, in order to generate revenue, we permit ad servers and other third parties (discussed below) to collect information via cookies for marketing as well.

The cookies we use are either: (a) session cookies (temporary cookies that expire when you log off the Site or when your session automatically times out) that maintain your session and maintain security and verify details while you use the Site as you navigate from page to page; or (b) persistent cookies (cookies stored on your browser between sessions) to help uniquely recognize you or your browser and remember how you have used the Site.

We may use third-party vendors such as Google and Mixpanel to place first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) or we may allow Google or other ad servers to place third-party cookies (such as the Google DoubleClick cookie) to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to the Site.

You may opt-out of certain third-party cookies, as described in the sections that follow immediately below. Also, you may be able to choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you may be able to turn off all cookies. You can do this through your browser settings. If you turn cookies off, some features of the Site may be disabled and the Site may not function properly,

You can find more information about cookies at websites such as [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

## **Online tracking / Do-Not-Track signals**

We may use third-party advertising services to serve ads when you visit the Site, and we use third-party analytics services to help us understand and improve the usage of the Site and the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

We or a third party may collect your IP address or an anonymous identifier as well as other user data from your browser or device, together with other non-personal information about your visits to our Site and other websites, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you on our Site and other websites and/or to provide analytical information for our Site and other websites. We work with third parties (such as Twitter or Facebook) to collect user data for purposes of conversion tracking and serving ads targeted to users’ interests. You can learn more about [Twitter’s Policies for Conversion Tracking and Tailored Audiences](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20171365) and [Facebook’s Terms For Conversion Tracking, Custom Audiences From Your Website, and Custom Audiences](https://www.facebook.com/customaudiences/app/tos/?ref=u2u). You may exercise control over collection and use of information for targeted advertising in a number of ways, including as available at [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices) (includes Facebook and various third party ad servers), [www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) (includes other third party ad servers), and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Certain third parties, such as Twitter, may respond to Do-Not-Track signals placed through your browser.

Except as stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not knowingly allow other parties to collect PII about your online activities over time and across third-party websites when you use our Site.

Because the providers of Do-Not-Track and similar signals do not yet operate according to common, industry-accepted standards, we currently do not respond to those signals. For more information about Do-Not-Track, please visit [www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

## **Online Tracking – services Google provides to the Site**

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google uses cookies to enable it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our Site and other sites on the Internet. Google's advertising requirements are described in [Google's Advertising Policies](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548).

We have implemented the following Google services through the Site:

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting
  * DoubleClick Platform Integration

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Settings page](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated?hl=en). You can opt out of Google Analytics by using the [Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout), and you can opt out of interest-based advertising by Google and certain other third parties by using functionality available on the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) website.

## **Third-party links**

The Site may contain links to other websites, and other websites may link to the Site. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. Whenever you visit another website – via a link from the Site or otherwise – you should review the privacy policy of that other website. This Privacy Policy applies solely to PII obtained in connection with your use of our website, user forum, or mobile app (and to related information that we may obtain in connection with your use of social media channels, as described above).

## **Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide PII in connection with purchasing products or services from us may request a disclosure of what PII, if any, we have shared with other businesses for their own direct marketing purposes. Such a request may be made by sending an e-mail message to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#274448495346445367415350094e49) with “Request for California Privacy Information” in the subject line of the message. In response to such a request, we will provide information as required by the California law for the previous calendar year concerning such other businesses and the categories of PII, if any, that we have shared with them.

California residents between the ages of 13 and 17 may view, correct, or delete information provided by you or publicly posted by you, by accessing your account through the Site or other product or service as applicable and editing/deleting your Information. You may also ask us to delete posted content, by contacting us as stated in the Contact Us section below. We will be happy to review, update or remove information and/or content as appropriate. Note, however, that we may retain your information to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, or comply with legal requirements.

## **COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act)**

We do not knowingly collect or store any PII from children under 13. Children under the age of 13 are explicitly prohibited from using the Site or providing us with PII. We urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their names, addresses, phone numbers, or other PII without parental permission when online. Parents should familiarize themselves with their children’s online activities and with the parental controls available on consoles, mobile telephones, tablets, and other devices they provide to their children.

If we learn that PII of persons under the age of 13 years has been collected through the Site, we  will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. Please see the Contact Us section below for further details. Parents should contact us immediately if they have any concerns or if they wish to notify us that they believe PII has been collected from a child below the age of 13.

## **E-mail Communications**

If you register for our newsletter or for an account under the Site, or during other interactions with us, we may ask for your e-mail address. We may use your e-mail address for marketing, or to send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. We will separately obtain express or implied consent from you before contacting you whenever we are required to do so by law (such as the Canadian “anti-spam” law).

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future marketing e-mails, you may do so using the contact information set forth in the “Contact Us” section below.

## **Users Outside of the United States**

This is a U.S.-based Site. If you are a visitor to our Site from outside the United States, the information you provide may be collected, processed and stored directly on, or transferred to, servers in the United States. By use of the Site, you consent and agree to such international transfers of your PII. If you do not agree to the collection, processing, storage and transfer of your PII, you should not use the Site.

## **Sales, Mergers, and Acquisitions**

In the event of a sale or other transfer of ownership of one or more of our business units to a third party (whether by private sale, through operation of law, as part of a divestiture plan, or otherwise), we will provide PII to the persons and/or entities assuming control of such location or business unit.

**Contact Us**

For questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, contact us using the information below.

Beerock Studios  
329 Warren St Apt 2F  
Brooklyn, NY 11201  
United States  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#53303c3d27323027133527247d3a3d)

## **Notification of Changes to Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, including as a result of changes to our business practices or applicable law. We will post notice of any material changes to our Privacy Policy on our website for a limited time. Regardless, you should be sure to review our Privacy Policy from time to time to be sure you are aware of the most recent version. We will handle PII in accordance with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time the information was collected.
